circleofcricket.co 2018-08-28

# 

This privacy policy will govern the use of the Website, Application and associated Service(s) developed/provided by TSD Corporation Ltd This Privacy Policy statement shall apply to all users who visit and access circleofcricket.com website and mobile application (collectively referred to as "Website"). The users unconditionally agree that browsing the Website and/or using its services signifies their unconditional assent to this Privacy Policy. 

#####  1\. Collection of Information

In general, you can visit our website without revealing your identity or any Personal Information about yourself. However, you may not be able to access certain areas or services that require registration or need you to reveal your identity and/or other information about you. Information that we collect from you will vary depending upon the activity you seek to engage in and may include your name, email address, phone number, mobile number, home address, date of birth. In addition, we may collect demographic information such as gender, information about your computer, hardware, software, platform, media, Internet Protocol (IP) address and connection, information about online activity such as feature usage and click paths, and other data that you may provide in surveys or online profiles. We may combine demographic information with Personal Information to tailor our offerings or web pages to your preferences or interests. 

##### 2\. Uses of Personal Information

We may use Personal Information and other information received and collected from you to provide the services you have requested, including services that display customized content and to contact you upon your request and when otherwise necessary. We may also use Personal Information for auditing, research and analysis, and to operate and improve our services. In certain circumstances, we may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties. When we use third parties to assist us in processing your Personal Information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. We may also share such information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.

##### 3\. Cookies

We set and access cookies on your computer’s hard drive or the memory component of your tablet, mobile or any other personal entertainment device(s), to track the preferences and trends of your searches in order to provide you with more personalized and improved services. You may reset the cookies to refuse such access by us. However, in such a case, you may not be able to access some parts or features of our Application.

##### 4\. Security and Confidentiality

We understand and recognize that privacy is very important. We take all the reasonable measures to protect the confidentiality of the information disclosed by You and will not disclose the information on any other forum other than Application and website and server associated thereof. We provide creation of password-protected account, which can be accessed only by You. We advise You to not share Your password with any other person and always log out before closing the browser window.

##### 5\. Third Party Disclosure

We will not disclose any of Your information to any third parties unless we are bound by law to do so. We may however disclose it to our trusted service providers or suppliers who help us in providing Service(s) to You.

##### 6\. Disclosure of Certain Information

In certain cases where we are bound by the provisions of law to disclose certain information to a law enforcing agency or to a court of law, or in cases where we are directed by a competent law enforcing agency to carry out an investigation into the activities of your account, we may do so without a notice to you. Such disclosure or investigation will not amount to breach of any privacy obligations on our part.

##### 7.Contacting You

We may contact you using the Personal Information you have given us: in relation to the functioning of any service you have signed up for in order to ensure that we can deliver the services to you; where you have opted to receive further correspondence; to invite you to participate in surveys about the our services (participation is always voluntary); and to provide you information about our new products and services, where you have specifically agreed to receive this.
